Bullets. Blood. Bingo.
He Never Died is a comedy, drama, fantasy film directed by Jason Krawczyk.
Jack is a solitary man with a mysterious past.
His strange habits will soon become stranger when his past catches up with him.
Jack, played by Henry Rollins.
Jeremy, played by Booboo Stewart.
Cara, played by Kate Greenhouse.
Andrea, played by Jordan Todosey.
Steve, played by David Richmond-Peck.
Short, played by James Cade.
He Never Died is a 2015 Canadian/American horror comedy film
that was written and directed by Jason Krawczyk.
It had its world premiere on March 17, 2015 at South by Southwest and stars Henry Rollins as Jack, an
immortal, cannibalistic loner who has withdrawn from society to protect both himself and others.
Plans were announced to create a direct sequel and
miniseries expansion following the character Jack.
The script for this was later rewritten to create the 2019 film She Never Died.
Filming for He Never Died began in November 2013 in Toronto
and concluded in December of the same year.
The film was released on various video on demand platforms as well as on DVD
and became available worldwide on Netflix on March 18, 2016.
The film explores themes of vampire, bible, flesh eating,
immortal, father daughter relationship.
The tone is dark and lighthearted and emotional.